Guide to the Darlington Autograph Files, 1610-1914 DAR.1925.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Sir William Gooch to Anthony Palmer, June 30, 1747 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- George H. Gordon to William Croghan Jr., August 22, 1827 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- George H. Gordon to William Croghan Jr., September 29, 1829 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Great Britain, Order to Pay William Turner, accompanied by handwritten transcript, June 26, 1648 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Great Britain, Order of Council for cannons for forts on the Ohio, Handwritten copies of papers held by the British Museum commissioned by William M. Darlington, August 10, 1753 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Great Britain, Lord Justices Warrant, June 4, 1755 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Great Britain army, Return of an allowance in lieu of island pay from October 1, 1800 to December 31, 1800 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Great Britain Privy Council, Royal order repealing two acts of assembly of Pennsylvania, July 7, 1756 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Nathaniel Greene to John Sanford Dort, June 30, 1783 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Thomas Grey to Hannah Penn, November 30, 1713 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Thomas Grey to Hannah Penn, January 15, 1713/14 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Miller Hageman to George K. Turner, Letter and articles, March 4, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Basil Hall to William E. Parry, May 1824 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Alexander Hamilton to Henry Jackson, August 19, 1794 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- James Hamilton to George Clinton, May 10, 1753 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- James Hamilton to Robert Hunter Morris, July 25, 1756 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Moses Hampton to John Covode, March 31, 1858 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- H. Hamtranck to --, April 26, 1784 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Daniel Hanagan to James O'Hara, October 20, 1802 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- George W. Hancock to William Croghan Jr., March 25, 1827 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- George W. Hancock to William Croghan Jr., December 15, 1828 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, June 2, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, June 4, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, July 6, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, July 29, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Edward Hand to James Perry, August 6, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, August 22, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, October 13, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, October 18, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, November 5, 1777 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry and Daniel McFarland, January 14, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, March 22, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, May 14, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, June 14, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, July 9, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, July 10, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Edward Hand to Archibald Lochry, July 27, 1778 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Edward Hand to Colonel Dayton, December 29, 1785 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Richard Harison, Receipt of payment, ca. April 1790 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Josiah Harmar, United States Army monthly return signed by Harmar, March 1, 1785 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Josiah Harmar to Ensign Armstrong, June 6, 1785 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Josiah Harmar to Henry Lee, May 18, 1790 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Mary Harris to [Hannah Penn], December 1, 1712 or 1713 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- W. D. Harris to Dr. A. N. McDomu, September 28, 1829 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Francis Rawdon Hastings, 2nd Earl of Moira, Promise to pay, June 9, 1809 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Francis Rawdon Hastings, 2nd Earl of Moira, to Washington Shirley, August 1, 1810 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Francis Rawdon Hastings, 2nd Earl of Moira, to C. B. Brampton, January 19, 1813 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Francis Rawdon Hastings, 2nd Earl of Moira, to Sir Hudson Lowe, November 9, 1817 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Selina Hastings, Countess of Huntingdon to Henry Laurens, May 6, 1784 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- John Hay to David Thompson Watson, November 10, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Robert Young Hayne to Robert Gilmor, October 23, 1827 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- John Heckewelder to Polly Heckewelder [in German], May 14, 1806 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Daniel Henchman, Account with Thomas Hancock, June 30, 1758 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- James Hendricks, Land survey of Turkey Hill for John Semple, October 30, 1769 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Alexander Henry to John V. Henry, January 4, 1801 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Patrick Henry to --[brother-in-law], May 15, 1786 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- A. Herring to William Croghan Jr., October 16, 1827 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Elbert Herring to William Wilkins, May 15, 1832 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- John Heth, Promissory note to William Fowler, on the reverse Fowler forwards payment to Robert Paris, April 1 and May 17, 1762 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- William Heth to Thomas Nelson, May 5, 1801 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Thomas Heyden to --, August 12, 1850 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Anthony Higgins to John Covode, August 11, 1868 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Wills Hill, 2nd Viscount Hillsborough, to Sir William Johnson (Duplicate No. 17), December 4, 1771 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Peter Hog to -----, September 22, 1757 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Thomas Holme, Instructions from William Penn, ca. 1682 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Thomas Holme to William Penn [duplicate], January 10, 1693 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Thomas Holme to William Penn [duplicate], December 20, 1693 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Thomas Holme to William Penn [duplicate], June 9, 1694 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Belle Horne to her sister, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- George Hosmer to Henry O'Reilly, Indian speeches from November 1816,May 5, 1837 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- John Hughes, Statement of account, 1795 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Joseph Hunter to John Wainwright, July 9, 1822 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Thomas Hutchins to George Morgan, January 31, 1769 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Thomas Hutchins to John Baynton, February 8, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Harry Innes to John Coburn, November 24, 1809 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Enoch Innis Deposition, December 20, 1768 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- William Irvine to The President of the State of Penna. [William Moore]with typed transcript, December 3, 1781 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- William Irvine to William Moore, May 2, 1782 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- William Irvine to William Moore, July 25, 1782 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- William Irvine to William Moore, October 8, 1782 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- William Irvine to John Dickinson, June 3, 1783 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- William Irvine to John Dickinson, August 16, 1783 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- William Irvine to John Nicholson, October 26, 1783 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- William Irvine to Joseph Clay, December 28, 1802 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- William Irvine to --, July 24, 1804 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Sir Henry Irving to -- Jones, January 21, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Andrew Jackson to Governor John Sevier, May 13, 1797 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Andrew Jackson, Provision return for flour, March 31, 1813 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- William Jack to Edward Hand, March 18, 1778 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- William Jack to Edward Hand, April 8, 1778 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Thomas Jefferson, Blank military commission signed by Jefferson, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Thomas Jefferson to Harrison Hall, April 3, 1818 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- William Jessup to William Croghan Jr., February 12, 1842 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- William Jessup to William Croghan Jr., February 14, 1842 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- William Jessup to William Croghan Jr., April 30, 1842 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Sir William Johnson to Governor Delancey, June 27, 1755 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Sir William Johnson to Henry Van Schaak, April 24, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Francis Johnston to James Wilson, May 27, 1777 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- David Jones to the Supreme Executive Council of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, April 18, 1787 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Simon Kenton, Article of agreement, May 10, 1804 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Isaac C. Ketler to James C. McFarland, August 3, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- David Tenney Kimball Jr. to John Rogers Kimball, November 17, 1836 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Rufus King to Benjamin Walker, February 15, 1795 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Henry Knox to Henry Jackson, August 31, 1796 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- H. W. Kriebel to Alfred P. Lee, January 7, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Jacob Kruyter, Authorization by Thomas Penn for the surveyal of land, August 2, 1738 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- David Kurtz to George W. Haller, Indenture, April 19, 1825 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Mary L'Amy to Mrs. General O'Hara, August 27, 1824 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Marquis de Lafayette to Monsieur Baradere [in French], undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Marquis de Lafayette, Fragment of a letter with his signature, July 8, 1778 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Caleb Lamb memorial from March 25, 1757, Handwritten copies of papers held by the British Museum commissioned by William M. Darlington (Box 4, Folder 42)
- William Larimer, Jr. to John Covode, November 25, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Charles Lebrun to -- [in French], February 7, 1802 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Charles Lefebvre-Desnoettes, Count to Jean-Gerard Lacuee, Comte de Cessac, January 29, 1813 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Letter to the inhabitants along the frontier, July 14, 1763 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Andrew Lewis to William Preston, August 27, 1757 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Thomas Lewis to --, August 20, 1757 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Earl John Ligonier to Charles Townshend, March 31, 1761 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Julius Lippert to A. G. Keller [in German], October 23, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Lawrence Litchfield to P. C. Knox, March 3, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Lawrence Litchfield to P. C. Knox, April 14, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- John R. Livingston to William Croghan Jr., July 17, 1827 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Robert R. Livingston to --, March 10, 1809 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Archibald Lochry to Edward Hand, March 30, 1778 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- James Logan to James Steel, March 23, 1719 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- The Lords of the Committee, Report for repealing two acts passed in Pennsylvania in August and November 1755 and Objections to Supply Act [duplicates], June 24, 1756 and June 1764 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- John Lukens, Surveyal contract [duplicate with Lukens' signature], April 11, 1789 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- P. Lyman to Reverend Eleazer Wheelock, September 26, 1767 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Aulay Babington Macaulay, Account of Jamaican earthquake, January 14, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Aeneas Mackay to Messrs Barnard and Michael Gratz, June 23, 1760 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Aeneas Mackay to Messrs Barnard and Michael Gratz, June 9, 1769 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Aeneas Mackay to James Wilson, April 9, 1774 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Aeneas Mackay, Queries to the Commissioners, October 10, 1776 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Richmond M. MacLeod to William Croghan Jr., January 31, 1842 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Richmond M. MacLeod to William Croghan Jr., February 3, 1842 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- William Markham to William Penn, First four pages with a transcript of the remainder of letter held by the PA Historical Society, March 27, 1684 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- William Markham to [William Penn], October 8, 1686 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Luther Martin to --, July 13, 1807 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- George Mason to Arthur Lee, March 24, 1784 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- William B. McBride to Alabama McBride, November 29, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Benjamin McCans et al. to Gentlemen, April 28, 1798 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- James Howard McHenry to Mrs. James P. Boyd, October 5, 1832 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- James Howard McHenry to Mrs. James P. Boyd, July 8, 1833 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Lachlan McIntosh to Archibald Lochry, September 6, 1778 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Lachlan McIntosh to Archibald Lochry, October 30, 1778 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Lachlan McIntosh to Archibald Lochry, March 9, 1779 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Lachlan McIntosh to Alexander Hamilton [duplicate], October 7, 1791 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Alexander McKee to Sir William Johnson, September 1, 1773 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Alexander McKee to Barnard Gratz, January 16, 1775 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- McKewan & O'Hara, Statement of accounts payable to McKewan & O'Hara1788 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Michael McKewan to James O'Hara, May 16, 1789 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- William McKinley, Jr. to Friend Case and family, June 21, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Thomas McKean and William Irvine to Governor Thomas Mifflin, August 22, 1794 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- Return Jonathan Meigs to Joanna Hand, May 22, 1795 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Charles Fenton Mercer to John C. Herbert, January 2, 1826 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- George Mercer to [Bouquet], December 27, 1760 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Hugh Mercer to Governor Denny,September 15, 1759 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Hugh Mercer to --, December 8, 1760 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Hugh Mercer, Account with Adam Stephen, November 17, 1766 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Hugh Mercer, Statement of account for 1762 and 1763, July 30, 1768 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Thomas Mifflin to Jacob Reed, December 21, 1784 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Benjamin Miller to General Forbes, Bill, November 27, 1758 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Charles Mitchell to Joseph C. Yates, May 18, 1823 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Robert Monckton to Gates, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Robert Monckton to --, October 30, 1760 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Samuel Moorhead to Edward Hand, January 14, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Mrs. H. Moreau to M. Cottinueau [in French], undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Jean Victor Marie Moreau to the minister of war [in French], February 9, 1796 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Jean Victor Marie Moreau to Mrs. Moreau [in French], March 28, 1809 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Daniel Morgan to Benjamin Biggs, April 2, 1795 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Daniel Morgan to Alexander Addison, June 8, 1795 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- George Morgan to Edward Hand, August 27, 1777 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Zackwell Morgan, Council of War Resolutions signed by Morgan, April 10, 1777 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Gouverneur Morris to Richard Varick, January 20, 1800 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Robert Hunter Morris to Mr. Lawrence, March 14, 1745 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Robert Hunter Morris, et al., Order for the sum of 2,000 pounds granted for his Majesty's use [duplicate], June 6, 1756 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- James Morrison to Samuel Smith, April 10, 1820 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Thomas Morrison to David Thompson Watson, November 10, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Thomas Morrison to David Thompson Watson, December 22, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Robert Moyer to John Hall, April 7, 1770 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Shedrick Muchmore, Survey [duplicate], November 5, 1770 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Joachim Napoleon Murat [in French], March 3, 1811 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- John Murray, 4th Earl of Dunmore to Colonel Martin, April 25, 1774 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- John Murray, 4th Earl of Dunmore, Certification of James Hamilton's military service, September 30, 1784 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- John Murray, 4th Earl of Dunmore to George Chalmers, August 19, 1795 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- William Murray et al., Articles of agreement, November 7, 1770 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Napoleon I to the minister of war [in French], February 12, 1800 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Louisa Neal, Elegy, April 12, 1816 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Joseph Neilson, Account of losses due to French encroachment, April 7, 1762 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Presley Neville to Colonel --, April 1778 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Presley Neville, Receipt, September 29, 1789 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Daniel Newman, Receipt signed by Newman, October 17, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Frederick North, 2nd Earl of Guilford to --, December 3, 1783 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Joseph Nourse to McKewan & O'Hara, May 19, 1789 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- John Ormsby to James Willson, March 29, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- George Ott, Specifications for four Green Street tenement houses, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
- John Owens, Deposition, April 1769 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- William Hemans Paddock to John Covode, March 8, 1864 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- William Hemans Paddock to John Covode, December 18, 1869 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Hugh Parker vs. George Croghan Writ of attachment for debt, April 26, 1750 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Samuel H. Parsons to Henry Laurens, January 20, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Henry Pearson, Certification of oath of allegiance to King, December 12, 1776 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- James Pemberton to Robert Morris, November 14, 1777 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Hannah Penn to William Lickfold, February 2, 1714 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- [John Penn to --], undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
- John Penn to [Peter Collinson], July 5, 1737 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- John Penn to Peter Collinson, January 13, 1738 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- John Penn to Peter Collinson, December 14, 1738 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- John Penn to Peter Collinson, December 24, 1738 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- John Penn to Peter Collinson, February 22, 1738/39 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- John Penn to [Peter Collinson], March 8, 1738/9 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- John Penn to [Peter Collinson], April 3, 1739 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- John Penn to Peter Collinson, June 6, 1739 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- John Penn to Peter Collinson, June 10, 1739 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- John Penn, Jr., Indenture between John Penn Jr., John Penn and George Clark, April 2, 1785 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Richard Penn to the Assembly, February 5, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Thomas Penn to Ferdinand John Paris, June 3, 1731 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Thomas Penn to William Penn, September 30, 1732 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Thomas Penn to [John Penn], July 21, 1733 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Thomas Penn to [John Penn], October 11, 1733 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Thomas Penn to John Penn, March 27, 1734 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Thomas Penn to William Penn, March 20, 1735 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Thomas Penn to a cousin, November 25, 1736 [duplicate] and December 8, 1736 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Thomas Penn to a cousin, December 8, 1736 [duplicate] and March 25, 1737 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Thomas Penn, Extracts of letters to and from Colonel Thomas and John Penn, August 8, 1744, February 27, 1745, and Nov 27, 1745 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Thomas Penn to Ferdinand John Paris, December 19, 1754 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Thomas Penn to Benjamin Chew, September 10, 1762 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Thomas Penn to Sir William Johnson, April 14, 1764 [duplicate] and May 12, 1764 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Thomas Penn to Benjamin Chew, December 7, 1764 [duplicate] and January 11, 1765 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Thomas Penn and Richard Penn to the Mayor of Commonality of Philadelphia, July 20, 1765 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Thomas Penn to Sir William Johnson, August 9, 1766 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Thomas Penn to Benjamin Chew, August 15, 1766 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Thomas Penn to [Richard] Hockley, November 20, 1766 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Thomas Penn to Sir William Johnson, March 3, 1770 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Thomas Penn to Benjamin Chew, February 18, 1772 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- William Penn to Jack [John Penn], September 17, 1734 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- William Penn, Instructions to William Markham, ca. 1683 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- William Penn, Privy Council Order by his Majesty dividing land between Lord Baltimore and Penn, September 7, 1685 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- William Penn Letters, 1666-1787 (Box 5, Volume 1)
- Pennsylvania Commissioners of Property, Order for a survey and division of land, December 30, 1720 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Pennsylvania militia, Pay roll for the militia at Pittsburgh for September and October, 1776 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Pennsylvania petition for relief [duplicate], March 3, 1756 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Peters Township Advertisement for loyal volunteers, May 25, 1765 (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Pennsylvania Historical Commission, Transcript of text Honoring Gen. John Armstrong (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Pennsylvania, Militia list of returned provisions in store at Pittsburgh signed by Hugh Mercer,April 4, 1759 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Packet Index 1785, 1791, July-December 1801, 1806 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania Republican Party, People's State Committee to John Covode, Request to speak, August 6, 1860 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Richard Peters to Council of Safety, November 8, 1776 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Bernard Peyton to George Hancock, March 4, 1824 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Timothy Pickering, Speech to Indians, November 22, 1790 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- John Pitcher to Samuel Walker, June 18, 1846 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Pittsburgh and Erie Rail Road Company Stock Certificates (2), September 5, 1855 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Benjamin Rush Plumly to John Covode, December 2, 1862 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Mrs. Potts, Receipt of payment for tuition and supplies to John Wigton, 1790 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Thomas Pownall to Sir William Johnson, October 13, 1755 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Thomas Pownall to [Joshua Thorpe], September 25, 1785 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Francis Preston to --, March 11, 1824 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Augustine Prevost to --, March 17, 1771 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Augustine Prevost, Receipt for Robert McCulloh, January 19, 1780 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Thomas Price, Petition to Robert Dinwiddie, March 10, 1756 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Thomas Priest, Petition to the representatives of the freemen of Pennsylvania, November 15, 1787 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Prince William County, Virginia Petition of clerks to Lieutenant Governor Francis Fauquier, ca. 1762 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thomas Procter to Owen Biddle, June 8, 1776 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Thomas Procter to Owen Biddle, March 1, 1777 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- John Randolph to [St. George Tucker], May 16, 1803 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Thomas Read, Opinion on a deed, March 8, 1798 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Red Jacket's Speech delivered at Washington as interpreted by Jasper Parish, February 11, 1801 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Colonel Reid to Thomas Gage, Extract of a letter, June 1, 1765 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Daniel Roberdeau to Mark Alexander, December 26, 1780 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Jonathan Roberts to William Jones, January 22, 1817 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Andrew Robertson, Authorization by Charles Biddle for the surveyal of land, October 17, 1785 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Henry B. Robertson, Deed of Trust [duplicate], May 12, 1826 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- M. Robinson to --, November 26, 1864 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- John Rodgers to Oliver Wolcott, June 28, 1817 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- John Rogers Kimball to Reverend David Tenney Kimball and family, November 10, 1839 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- I. G. Rosengarten to Charles W. Dahlinger, September 4, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Alexander Ross to Dear Lads, September 14, 1774 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- James Ross, Title pages of John Reeves' 1787 History of the English Law signed by Ross, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
- James Ross to Lawrence Lewis, July 1, 1801 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- James Ross to Jonathan Smith, July 29, 1803 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- James Ross Indenture, November 13, 1829 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Samuel Ross to Lawrence Lewis, October 18, 1800 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Mary Russell to [Hannah Penn], October 4, 1713 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- A S. to Thomas Evered, January 19, 1641 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- St. Clair heirs vs. Shale and Kennedy, Depositions for lawsuit over land, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Arthur St. Clair to Elias Boudinot, October 7, 1778 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Arthur St. Clair vs. Timothy Turnout [duplicate], 1775-1779 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Arthur St. Clair to Mordecai Gist, December 7, 1781 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Arthur St. Clair Land Survey [duplicate], October 21-23, 1783 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Arthur St. Clair to John Nicholson, June 21, 1789 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Arthur St. Clair to Captain Armstrong, December 2, 1791 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Arthur St. Clair to George Simpson, June 27, 1798 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- John St. Clair to [Elizabeth] Betsy Graeme, July 28, 1757 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- W. Sargent to County Lieutenants [duplicate], February 12, 1791 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Edward W. Schenley to William Croghan Jr. (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Edward W. Schenley to William Croghan Jr. (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Edward W. Schenley to Mr. Lynch (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Melchior Scholtze to Jan Enscheede [in German], March 9, 1737 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Philip John Schuyler to Captain --, August 3, 1773 (Box 6, Folder 55)